hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and on this podcast I
talk about ways for you to grow in your
life and in your business to be able to
make more money impact more people and
live the life your dreams now
today I'm going to be playing a video
game uh called Dark Souls 2 it's one of
my favorite games it's one of the
hardest games that exists I'm towards
the end of the game so I have a really
overpowered
character um you know you can kind of
see his statistics right
here uh all the different player stats
that I have and all that um so you can
see it in the lower corner as far as
this
goes H again this is part of a new kind
of trial run of doing podcast episodes
while I play various video games and
this one I like cuz basically you level
up your character you de feed all these
crazy bosses and it's just it's hard
it's kind of like business a little bit
it reminds me of business in a way that
it's so
difficult uh you know to
defeat but it's so worth it
to keep striving to do that and so what
I want to talk about today is it's a
it's part of the dance of making
money
um in your business it's part of the
dance
of striving and it's one of the things
that I think a lot of people get wrong
when it comes to their businesses online
they're focused in on the wrong stuff
they're they're they're really focused
in on the thing that's not going to
produce money for them and that's the
problem that I see with so many coaches
and mentors is being focused on stuff
that doesn't actually produce cash flow
all
right there we go awesome so my
character didn't even get scratched
right
there so one of the issues that I that I
see
is
that many business owners are way too
concerned
with what other people might think about
them how they might appear to other
people and I often hear this you know
you only have one shot at a first
impression so don't mess it up this type
of thinking is
obviously uh there's some truth to that
of
course but I don't worry about what my
first impression is with people with
what they think about me with what their
opinions of me are why is that
well because to to be honest um I've
made a decision to not build a business
in a
codependent fashion
overall and um Co codependency means
that I that I am more
worried
and giving more effort to your success
than you're even willing to give
yourself and that's just not something
that I
am ever really willing to do in in
business
bu when it comes to sales often times I
see people in the beginning striving
struggling trying to make people buy
from them and and trying to make people
understand what they do now there comes
a time where yes you got to speak truth
to get people to
act I was just talking about my mom
about that today is like some people
really need to like be woken up from
their they're sort of I guess you could
say like
Slumber as it
were they Slumber is
that they you know they need they need
somebody sometimes to just say the tough
things to actually wake them up out of
not
doing what it's going to take for them
to succeed of course
right but ultimately
um you know what does that look like
that that that looks
like you being willing to let people go
you being willing to let people fail you
being willing to even if people reject
your offer even if people don't buy into
it even if people
um say hey I don't want this it's not
your job to convince any of them that
they should quote un quote change their
mind or do anything
differently uh based on this and so
that's one of the things that I that I
often tell a lot of the coaches and
mentors that I meet is that you're
working way too hard on other people's
success managing their feelings managing
their opinions way too deep when in fact
it's time to just kind of give up that
Crown all together and and just focus on
the ones who truly love to engage with
you the ones who actually are connecting
with your message and the ones that are
actually doing something with you and
listen not everybody is going to do
anything with what you give them as far
as that goes and so hey keep that in
mind that oh man and there I died you
died a man well I did not do good there
it's not your job to make any
anybody buy from you I'm okay with 100%
if somebody just
completely rejects me just
completely
wants nothing to do with me in my
business um and even badmouths me or
said stuff and I never have to defend
myself and and what we found is that
when you run Facebook
ads often times
ads
um the more negative comments you get
actually the better overall and I know a
lot of some coaches I know some very
successful mentors and coaches who
strive so hard to not have any negative
comments come in on their social media
they're really focused in on like this
whole like managing my reputation
thing and they see it as themselves I
guess being a bad coach if anybody has a
bad experience with them and that
everybody should quote unquote get a
result from what they're doing here's
the thing you could have the best
coaching the best course the best
training and people will still not get a
result because people are people and
also that's not not every offer
works sometimes we're we still have
to test
no sometimes we still have to test our
offers out
we have to test new offers out just to
kind of you know see what
happens and not all the time will they
will they work
but it's still part of the process to at
least at least try and one of the
biggest things that I see that people do
is they're afraid of things not working
out and so they don't
do anything really in their business
overall because they let
fear sort of run them they let the
fear kind of kind of control
them and so what you got to learn how to
do is you got to learn how to not
let these types of
situations get you knocked up you're
going to sell more when you stop trying
to control manage and maintain what
other people do and you learn to
disqualify people that aren't a good fit
for you that's one of the biggest
amateur mistakes I see people make is
they're trying to say well you I don't
want to miss out on anybody I don't want
to miss
opportunity and the fear of missed
opportunity really is a is a is a
poverty mindset it's a lack mindset it's
rooted
in um stuff that's just not even good
for you because it's going to lead you
to do things that are actually going to
hurt you in the long run but you're
going to think that you're helping
yourself and that's what I see a lot of
coaches and mentors do is they
are they're afraid of what everybody
might think about them they don't want
to set a bad impression quote unquote a
bad first impression and so what they do
is they
literally spend all their effort trying
to make sure that people buy into what
they're saying I don't want to offend
anybody I don't want to say anything
that upsets anybody when the truth is if
you upset or offend people the ones that
are not that don't like you you want
them out of your space quickly the ones
that don't resonate with you and it's
not that you're trying to get people to
hate you you're but you can
automatically have people that do that
just simply because you exist or breathe
air on planet Earth and
so it's not it's not your job to
get anybody
to change
or believe in you or or buy into buy
into
anything it's not your job to to do that
your job is
to present the opportunity as best as
you
can and if they reject it if they say no
that's not on you to get them to quote
unquote change their mind or do
something differently okay and so I
think that once you like once you get
that and once you start to operate from
that framework of how you live your life
and how you build your business like I'm
talking like this is a complete life
change thing this is a completely
different way of even
thinking and doing life
overall is not as being
completely and utterly unconcerned
if quote
unquote somebody doesn't become a client
of yours or buy from
you and that you just simply focus on
the ones who really truly
do resonate with your message overall
and you're not trying to convince
anybody that they
should change their mind about you or do
anything differently and I think that
that is that's a powerful position to
take in your business it's a position of
power that allows you to have the kind
of impact that actually you're truly
meant to have and I and I meet a lot of
people where they're not doing this
where they're afraid of losing people or
they're afraid of losing business where
they're afraid of missing out
on the ultimate like opportunity or
missing out on helping even somebody and
that they have it built up in their mind
this whole idea that okay I have to
always help people or I'm a bad person
they have to always get a transformation
and listen not everybody's going to get
a transformation from you overall so
keep that in mind that sometimes it's
okay if people don't get a
transformation from you if
they if they if they meet you and they
work with you and then maybe like
something doesn't work out you got to
stop being worried about disappointing
other people overall if you if you ever
in your business want to actually be
financially successful because you could
do the greatest things and yet you will
still have people that don't like you
overall that just are not they don't
resonate with you for whatever reason
they don't connect with you and and it's
not your job to convince them otherwise
that they should ever period end of
story there we go we just defeated the
boss that's great Victory
achieved and so that's just that's what
I wanted to share with you in this
podcast is that you're going to make a
lot more money when you
stop
trying to control manage
maintain really anything from
anybody
period
overall and and and I just I see this so
often with coaches
trainers
mentors great
people who have great impact that impact
the world around
them that are doing great things that
have the potential for just absolutely
incredible levels of
greatness in their
lives
and
you can't defeat this guy right
here and yet they're so concerned with
making themselves look
good people connect you know connecting
with them and being afraid to lose a
sale being afraid of people disliking
them being afraid of people judging them
a certain way you know this is why like
me playing a video game like this even
with the pauses that I'm doing and all
that you know I used to be so concerned
with how I sound and how I look on all
my podcast episodes now I'm just like
you know
what I
am
completely
unconcerned by this this is
cool I've really progressed a lot
further in the
game than I ever did I guess I'm a I
guess I'm I'm the king it's awesome cuz
I got the king's
ring and the king's Ring really is uh
one of the biggest uh things that you
want
to to have that's
cool where is the king's Ring king's
ring bell keeper king's ring it opens
the king's gate all right awesome let's
go to the king's gate
then stop worrying about what people
think about
you stop worrying about do they dislike
you
stop worrying about are you going to
miss out on a potential sale because you
offend somebody upset somebody they
don't like how you do something there I
guarantee you there are people right now
they will not ever listen to me again
because they see me playing this game
and I'm okay with that and when you get
to that place where you are
truly
unconcerned about what anybody thinks
about
you and you truly do not
give
a
rip at
all about anybody's opinions about you
you can make a ton more money you're
losing
money by ever being
concerned with what anybody thinks about
you or what they do or if they buy from
you or if they're
that you know if they're being worried
that you're going to possibly miss
out on any of those
things I mean that just really is like
one of the guaranteed ways to make sure
that you don't make any money and and my
and for me when I was building my
business worrying
about am I making enough money am I
connecting with people am I going to
lose money all
that is just
just it was really
like one of the one of the greatest
things that stopped me from
succeeding reaching my my goals
overall and
um and now for
me I I have
found that I've been able to grow
in these areas
by being unconcerned being able to grow
my bottom line being able to grow
financially
overall by being
truly
unconcerned with are they going to like
me are they going to resonate with me
are they going to be able to connect
with me are they am I going to lose
somebody because you know they're
opinion of me
somehow uh is negative because I'm doing
or said something or because I didn't do
something and and because of that so
again and hear me out I'm not saying
like you do anything that is Criminal
defrauding people anything like that
like people don't like you just because
of
like arbitrary things like as simple as
again me playing a video game
I've lost plenty of potential business
because of
that and I am perfectly okay with
that because I want to be myself and I
want to
be I don't want to be anybody that I'm
not simply to make people like me that's
that's called lying to
people
and I refuse to lie to
people for business or
money that's a line I won't
cross and so you know we live in an
industry where Integrity is at stake at
all
corners and
um your ability to
be
be able to just be yourself show up
however you
want regardless of what anybody might
think about you what they might say
whether you lose business if they go
blast your name everywhere and say all
this nasty stuff about you doesn't phase
me at all I don't spend time managing or
maintaining my reputation and I've
actually lost business because people
are concerned that I say that as to what
that looks like because they are way too
concerned about managing and maintaining
their reputation it's the fact is is
that what I care about is impacting
people number one that's one of the most
important things to me is having impact
on people's
lives uh you know changing people's
lives for the better is is something
that I
truly care about and think that I have
the ability to do as
well and so if you're if you're watching
this right now if you're listening to
this you're going to make a lot more
sales and you just stop worrying what
everybody thinks about you you stop
legitimately
caring if they dislike you or not
overall so I just I just want to
encourage you
that you know if you're somebody who
sitting on my couch here if you're
somebody who wants to make money in your
business you want to make more money and
you want to change your life you got to
stop truly worrying about am I going to
possibly lose a sale because of this and
this and this and be more bold be more
out there
be however you want to be and stop
worrying how they think of you and that
is going to change everything for you
all right all right listen if this has
helped you share it with
somebody grow your life everybody we'll
talk soon have a good
[Music]
one